"Mob Psycho 100"
"Namu Amida Butsu"
"Namu Amida Butsu" Believe it or not,
the world is filled with strange phenomena
"Namu Amida Butsu"
that science is yet to explain.
That science is yet to explain.
And when people come
face to face with them,
they are helplessly thrown
into the dark depths of fear.
But there are those who fight every day
to shine a ray of hope
into that chaotic darkness.
People call them...
"Psychics"
Psychics.
I, Reigen Arataka, shall accept this job!
"Reigen Arataka"
Really? Thank you so much!
I was at a complete loss because
no one else would take me seriously.
"Client: Hanako" I was at a complete loss
because no one else would take me seriously.
I was at a complete loss because
no one else would take me seriously.
I see, I see.
As for my fees, it depends on
which exorcism course you pick.
Course?
"Option A -- Trial Course" "A Mere 2,000 yen (Tax
Excluded) Outside of Offer Period: 3,980 yen"
"Option A -- Trial Course" "A Mere 2,000 yen (Tax Excluded) Outside
of Offer Period: 3,980 yen" Option A, the trial course, gets you 20%,
Option A, the trial course, gets you 20%,
"Option B -- Serious Course" "A Mere 5,000 yen (Tax Excluded) Outside
of Offer Period: 8,980 yen" Option A, the trial course, gets you 20%,
"Option B -- Serious Course" "A Mere 5,000 yen
(Tax Excluded) Outside of Offer Period: 8,980 yen"
"Option B -- Serious Course" "A Mere 5,000 yen (Tax Excluded) Outside
of Offer Period: 8,980 yen" Option B, the serious course, gets you 50%,
Option B, the serious course, gets you 50%,
"Recommended" " Option C -- All-Out Course" "A Mere 12,000
yen (Tax Excluded) Outside of Offer Period: 19,880 yen"
"Recommended" " Option C -- All-Out Course" "A Mere 12,000 yen (Tax Excluded) Outside
of Offer Period: 19,880 yen" and Option C, the all-out course, gets you a 99%...
and Option C,
the all-out course, gets you a 99%...
...reduction in spirit, guaranteed!
Reduction?
Well, spirits are sort of
like carbon dioxide.
They are?
Yes, well... that's the
kind of space they occupy,
so it's a bit hard
to completely get rid of one.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" so
it's a bit hard to completely get rid of one.
So it's a bit hard
to completely get rid of one.
But have no fear.
If it appears again,
I'll take care of it for 20% off!
Oh, Reigen-sense!
Hold on a second!
Hm? Who might you be?
This is my boyfriend, Taro.
Ah, what a benevolent fellow!
"Boyfriend: Taro"
What's that supposed to mean?!
Er, that aside...
Listen up, you! This is super shady!
Hanako, you should really rethink this.
"This is super shady"?!
I guess I can't blame you
for feeling that way.
I mean, who would believe a stupid story
like having nightmares about ghosts?
I wasn't talking about her!
I was saying that I can't trust you!
Well, just leave it to me.
If I exorcise the spirit,
I'm sure Hanako-san's face
will return to normal, too.
There's nothing wrong with her face!
I see.
So, you've been having those dreams ever
since you did a test of courage last week.
Yes. They're so scary and creepy.
Ah, Reigen-sensei,
it's that building over there!
What an incredible aura!
This is gonna be the first
big one I've had in a while!
Sensei, it's this building over here.
Wait, you just pointed at
the wrong building, didn't you?
Huh? Ah, so it's that one!
There was such an immense aura
emanating from over there, too.
I guess I got the wrong spirit!
There are way too many evil spirits
in this world, you know?
Ah, I see.
Please. There's no way
there are ghosts everywhere--
Oh, no!
That man who just
walked past you, Taro-san...
--What?
--What a close shave. That was an evil spirit, too.
The Buttchin Goblin.
What are you, eight?!
Hey, Taro, that's rude!
What? He's the one being rude
to that random guy.
Now, now, Hanako-san.
There are always people like him.
Anyway, shall we go?
This bastard...
They say this place is haunted by
the spirit of a man who saw a cockroach
and jumped so high, his head went
through the ceiling and he died.
I don't know how
you actually believe that.
I see.
So, that's what is going on here...
What? He suddenly looks all serious.
Could there really be...?
If worst comes to worst,
even I might not be able to handle it!
This is too dangerous!
Cockroaches are terrifying!
Huh?
There's no way this guy is a psychic!
He's a total fake!
Want me to haunt your dreams, too?
A ghost!
"Evil Spirit: Ceiling Crasher"”
"Evil Spirit: Ceiling Crasher"” Want me to
crash you through the ceiling with my curse?
Want me to crash you
through the ceiling with my curse?
That's the same guy who keeps
headbutting me in my dreams!
I can't believe he actually appeared.
I've got this!
Salt Splash!
"Salt Splash"
This is one of Reigen's special attacks,
where he violently
throws table salt everywhere.
This is just table salt you can buy in stores.
It has to be purified salt or it won't work.
"Hakata Salt"
Impossible...
Did I only imagine that
spirits are weak against salt?
Well, if salt won't melt it, I guess
I'll have to call my ultimate weapon.
Oh, Mob? Sorry, but could you come by?
No, seriously.
There's an evil spirit.
The client and the evil spirit
are both waiting,
so hurry up, okay?
Thanks.
Ah, Mob.
We were waiting for you.
Hmph. So after the salt,
you're using a middle schooler?
Quit looking down on--
He is Kageyama Shigeo,
also known as Mob.
"Kageyama Shigeo" He is
Kageyama Shigeo, also known as Mob.
He is Kageyama Shigeo,
also known as Mob.
"Mob" He is Kageyama
Shigeo, also known as Mob.
Mob
“Mob“
He's an actual psychic,
Mob
Reigen Arataka's student,
and the protagonist of this story.
Master, I asked you not to
summon me on such short notice.
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
Man, you're a lifesaver.
I never thought that an evil spirit
would actually show up.
Here. Your pay for the day.
Oh, thank you.
That one today was a lower-level spirit,
so I really shouldn't be
paying you more than half.
But I'll give you your hourly pay.
Think of it as a bonus.
Right...
What? Do you have a problem with that?
Oh, no. But the spirit back there
really was a lower-level spirit.
It was so weak, you...
Y-You idiot!
When you get to my level,
you get so strong
you end up melting everyone
around you during a simple exorcism.
That's why I ask you
to take care of the weaker ones.
Really?
I'm also not quite sure
what you mean by "melt," either...
Mob, you idiot!
That's because you lack training!
"The New Star of the 21st Century" "Reigen Arataka" "Spirits and Such
Consultation Office" Mob, you idiot! That's because you lack training!
"The New Star of the 21st Century"” "Reigen
Arataka" "Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"The New Star of the 21st Century" "Reigen Arataka" "Spirits and Such
Consultation Office" You need to learn everything you can from me, your master!
You need to learn everything
you can from me, your master!
Your powers are meant to be used.
Not doing so would be a waste.
Working for me lets you help others,
while also being training for you.
You're killing two birds with one stone!
However, if you misuse
a power that's all too great,
you will only destroy yourself.
That's why I'm teaching you how to control
your powers so they don't go berserk.
You promised me, didn't you?
That you wouldn't use your
psychic powers against other people.
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 22%"
Ah...
There you go again, bending spoons.
You really need to drop that habit.
Oh, come now.
Shigeo's going through puberty.
Let him bend some spoons. Right?
Heh, sorry.
And there you go, spoiling him again.
You need to learn from Ritsu, Shige.
He got another perfect score
on his quiz today.
Anyone can do that, Mom.
If there's anything troubling you,
let me know, Nii-san.
I'll be there to listen any time.
"Kageyama Ritsu”
Right. Thanks, Ritsu.
And now you're spoiling him, too, Ritsu.
The next one you bend gets replaced
using your allowance, you hear?
Huh?
Sorry, Nii-san.
There's nothing I can do about that.
Now you're in a real pickle, Shigeo.
"Seasoning City, Salt Middle School"
Morning!
"Salt Middle School"
Right?
Good morning, Tsubomi!
Morning!
It's such a beautiful day, isn't it?
Oh, yeah. On TV yesterday...
What?
Tsubomi-chan's as cute as ever today...
Okay, so, what would be the answer here?
Let's go with Kageyama.
Y-Yes, sir...
"Arithmetic |"
I have no idea.
"Arithmetic |" If you can't solve this, that'd
mean the only thing you know is addition.
"Arithmetic |"
You were asleep, weren't you?
Forget it. Sit down.
There it goes!
This way!
Pass, pass, pass!
--Go, go!
--Stop 'em!
--Pass, pass!
--Go!
"Reigen Arataka"
--Hello?
--Ah, Mob?
Sorry to call you two days in a row,
but could you come down
to the station right now?
The station?
Yeah. Today's job is a big one.
Oh. All right.
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 25%"
"Mob Psycho 100"
Today's job is from
a local neighborhood council.
The location is Honeido Tunnel
along the old highway.
"Famous Haunted Spot" "Terror" "Haunted" "Ghost" "Tunnel" "The location is the old
Seasoning Highway Honeido Tunnel" The location is Honeido Tunnel along the old highway.
"Famous Haunted Spot" "Terror" "Haunted" "Ghost" "Tunnel"
"The location is the old Seasoning Highway Honeido Tunnel"
"Famous Haunted Spot" "Terror" "Haunted" "Ghost" "Tunnel" "The location
is the old Seasoning Highway Honeido Tunnel" It's a famous haunted place.
"Famous Haunted Spot" "Terror" "Haunted" "Ghost" "Tunnel"
"The location is the old Seasoning Highway Honeido Tunnel"
"Famous Haunted Spot" "Terror" "Haunted" "Ghost" "Tunnel" "The location is the
old Seasoning Highway Honeido Tunnel" The tunnel's always had some shady stories,
The tunnel's always had some shady stories,
and even though it's been closed for years,
the bad rumors just won't go away.
Also, a number of college students
and bloggers have gone there
to do a test of courage and gone missing.
And this is the ringer.
"Honeido Tunnel Group Accident"
A huge group accident?
Yeah, though it happened thirty years ago.
Apparently, more than
twenty people died at once.
The hatred of all those people
must be swirling around this tunnel.
Stay on your toes, Mob.
There's no telling what might happen.
Oh, right.
"Honeido Tunnel"
This is it.
Well, let's take a look.
I, Reigen Arataka, the new star
of the paranormal world,
shall clean this place up.
We're going to exorcise
every last one of them, Mob.
Hey, my student!
What are you doing, Mob?
You're coming, too!
It'll be bad if the sun goes down.
Mob, are you listening?
I'm gonna go melt down
a big one, so follow me!
--Got it?
--All right.
You seemed to have
everything under control,
so I didn't think that you'd need my help.
You idiot! Who do you think
is going to exorcise--Ahem.
I mean, this really is nothing for me,
but follow me so you can learn something.
You're truly amazing, Master.
--Hm?
--This tunnel seems pretty dangerous.
I can sense the presence of
a very powerful spirit further down.
Usually, haunted spots end up being fake,
but this is definitely the real deal.
If a normal person happened
to anger the spirit in here...
If they angered it...?
They probably wouldn't
make it out in one piece.
Of course not.
That's why we're going to exorcise it.
All right, here we go!
I'll go first.
I'm counting on you to support me
however you can from behind.
Right.
It's a bit chilly.
Yes.
We forgot to bring flashlights.
Master, don't you feel something?
Hm? Well, it is pretty humid in here...
No, I'm talking about auras.
Oh, right, that.
Well, my nose is a bid sduffy do day.
Does that have anything to do with this?
When you get to my level, it does.
Do you feel anything?
Feel would be an understatement.
There are twelve...
Eighteen...
No... Even more right nearby.
Ah!
Looks like we've been
completely surrounded.
They're going to attack us now.
All right! I'll leave the small fry to you.
Go, Mob!
Man, that's a lot of noise.
They're really strong, huh?
Hmm... If we were normal people,
we might have been in danger.
Well, I'm sure that took care of all of them.
Another piece of ca--
There's someone right in front of me!
Who are you?! An evil spirit?!
"Boss"
Oh, it's just a heel wrestler.
Don't scare me like that!
I thought you were an evil spirit.
You shouldn't be practicing here.
Uh, Master.
The boss of sorts
of the evil spirits is over there,
so watch out.
"Evil Spirit: Boss"
Hmph, so you're the boss monkey
of the evil spirits!
You may have tried to disguise yourself
as a wrestler, but you can't fool me!
I---
This tunnel...
When my biker gang and I
were going down this tunnel,
the guy in front happened
to slip on a banana peel,
and we all died! And I'm their leader!
This tunnel is...
...my turf!
I'll crush every last intruder!
Here we go! Curse ya!
"Curse ya"
Cigarette Burn Poltergeist!
Wh-What?
My ignition attack isn't working?
There's a powerful force field?
How could this power
be coming from someone like him?
Crap! I mistook him for a wimp!
Too late for regrets now!
The moment that you tried to take on
the genius psychic, Reigen Arataka,
your fate was sealed!
You're going to be exorcised!
Banishing Salt Punch!
This is one of Reigen's special attacks,
"Banishing Salt Punch"
"Banishing Salt Punch" where he punches the
enemy with his fist covered in table salt.
Where he punches the enemy
with his fist covered in table salt.
Huh? That didn't hurt at all.
Oh, dear.
So, you are a fake...
I'm disappearing!
--Go back to the ozone layer.
--W-Wait! Wait!
We were just being forced to do this!
Hey, what are you doing, Mob?
Hurry up and melt him.
Now, now, Master.
Let's hear him out.
We're nothing compared to
the evil spirit down the tunnel.
We've been getting orders from him,
and that's why we've been
scaring people that come through.
Hmph. Don't think that you can
fool Reigen with such lies!
They aren't lies!
It's just that if I disappeared
while being falsely accused,
"Death Specters Gang" It's just that if I
disappeared while being falsely accused,
"Death Specters Gang"
"Death Specters Gang" I didn't
think that we, the Death Specters,
I didn't think that we,
the Death Specters,
"Boss"
and our memories could rest in peace!
That's all I wanted to say!
Now you can make me disappear,
melt, or whatever you want!
So, you're trying to make us pity you?
Don't let him fool you, Mob!
Those are the typical lies of a con artist.
Melt him.
Before that, I'm going to go have a look.
Huh?
I thought it was a little weird that the aura
I felt before coming in here
hadn't disappeared yet.
--Well, yeah, me, too...
--Stop him!
No matter how strong that kid may be,
he doesn't stand a chance.
That thing is an evil spirit that's lived
on this mountain for hundreds of years.
Everyone that's died here was killed by him!
S-So you guys were also...
No. We just happened
to slip on a banana peel.
You get it now, don't you?
If you care for that kid at all, call him back.
Hurry!
H-Hey, Mob! Come back!
Come back! Mob!
Mob?
Ah.
Oh, you're safe.
Yes. That evil spirit wasn't very powerful.
Wh-Who are you?
Huh? I'm nobody...
You idiot!
You're Mob, the student...
...of Reigen Arataka, the new star
of the paranormal world!
Oh, right.
I thank you.
Now we can all pass on peacefully.
Ah, could this be...
"Death Specters Gang"
Here we go, Boss!
Yeah!
"Death Specters Gang"
We, who live at the corner of the world
Thanks...
Will get beyond our tears and
head towards the light. Thanks...
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light.
Will get beyond our tears and head towards the light.
"Self-Proclaimed Psychic: Reigen Arataka” "~And Mob-~"
"Self-Proclaimed Psychic: Reigen Arataka"
"~And Mob~"
--Thanks, dude.
--Now we can depart to the afterlife!
Full speed ahead to the next world!
The dreams and ideals that we believe in
Mob.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Feel like they may shatter as soon as we take
our eyes off them What are you doing? Let's go.
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Feel like they may shatter as soon
as we take our eyes off them Right.
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Thousands, millions of distinct Flashbacks
"Bus Schedule"
Underneath the sky in slow motion,
So real that I want it to disappear.
By the way, Master...
Huh?
So real that I want it to disappear.
Why didn't you do anything?
My heart was stolen a second before the
unpredictable, Why didn't you do anything?
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
My heart was stolen a second before
the unpredictable, Well, uh, you know...
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
My heart was stolen a second
before the unpredictable, A-Ahem...
A-Ahem...
After being hurt on a whim
Didn't I tell you right at the start
something from somewhere
that I'd leave the small fry to you?
Something from somewhere
Oh, right.
Is overflowing and won't stop.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
Will get beyond our tears and head
towards the light "Seasoning Station"
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
What do you wanna do?
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred? We're looking
for the answer. What do you wanna do?
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred? We're looking
for the answer. Let's get something to eat.
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred? We're looking for
the answer. I'm not gonna last until I get home.
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred? We're
looking for the answer. I know, right?
I know, right?
But over and over again The sound in our
hearts resonates together I know, right?
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
But over and over again The sound in our hearts resonates
together Sorry to keep you waiting, Mob. Shall we?
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
But over and over again The sound
in our hearts resonates together Yes.
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
But over and over again The sound in our hearts
resonates together Does ramen work for you?
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
Yes.
"Yes n "No n
"Yes n "No n If you're going to
add on chashu pork, limit it to two.
If you're going to add on
chashu pork, limit it to two.
All right.
Here you go.
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 25%"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 26%"
"Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 27%"
A group of telepathics suddenly appear
and disturb Mob's daily life.
Having doubts about his peaceful youth,
Mob heads into a world of women.
Where is the goal?
Which way is tomorrow?
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 2:
"Doubts About Youth
- The Telepathy Club Appears~."
"Doubts About Youth"
"~The Telepathy Club Appears~"
"Doubts About Youth" "~The Telepathy Club
Appears~" Watching it in real time? Wise decision.
"Doubts About Youth"
"~The Telepathy Club Appears~"